[BARRIUS]
So, just kick them out?
[MAN] Yeah.
Trimming the excess fat is key.
I've heard lots of guilds
are doing that lately.
Maybe we should follow suit.
[MAN] Trust me,
the Beast's Fangs would
only benefit from some firings.
Kicking people out
is great for business.
Expenses go way down.
And the best part is
you don't have to look
at their stupid faces
every day you go to work.
[Barrius grunts]
You sold me on it!
Let's cut someone!
Sounds like fun.
The only question is, who?
♪
[guild member 1 grunts]
After that,
I definitely need a drink.
That's another successful
monster-slaying quest
in the books.
Don't tell me you numbskulls
are already done with the job.
[GUILD MEMBER 1] All we found
were weaklings.
[laughter]
[REIN] They're so lucky.
Getting the chance to fight.
[indistinct chatter]
[REIN] Me? I've never even
had the opportunity.
My role is Enchanter.
As long as I've been
with the guild,
I've focused on enhancing
everyone else's weapons
and equipment.
[GUILD MEMBER] Uh?
Move it, Rein.
Quit your daydreaming
and get back
to what we pay you for.
Right! Sorry about that.
Oh, not bad. Not bad at all.
With your fancy enchantments,
even a normal sword
can be a legendary blade.
I know.
[smirks] I almost forgot.
Follow me.
Guildmaster Barrius said
he wanted to have
a word with you. Let's go.
He wants to see me?
♪
[REIN] That shield...
That sword...
His armor and his axe.
Yours truly enchanted
each and every one.
I may not go into battle,
but in my own way
I contribute
to the guild's achievements.
Now Barrius has personally
asked for me.
I wonder what this is about.
Maybe I'm getting a raise.
Wait, what if
a famous adventurer
heard about my skills
and traveled from far away
to see if I would
enchant equipment for them?
That's gotta be it.
-You're fired, kid.
-[Rein gasps]
With all the powerful weapons
and armor we've got now,
there isn't any point
in keeping you around.
Besides, the only actual skill
you've got is enchanting items,
and what this guild
really needs are fighters.
You can't just let me go
if the pretext makes
literally zero sense.
♪
Still fired.
Come on, you heard the man.
Now, are you gonna
leave willingly,
or do I have to make you?
I still haven't accepted
this dumb decision.
That's not our problem, runt.
You wanna go? Bring it on!
[grunts]
Ouch. Yeah, I'm lacking
in battle experience,
but that doesn't mean
I can't become an adventurer.
[GUILD MEMBER 1] Shut up, Rein!
[GUILD MEMBER 2] Yeah,
you'll never be one of us!
[GUILD MEMBER 3] Who would
ever want to adventure with you?
[GUILD MEMBER 4]
All you can do is enchant.
You're just a weak,
useless, one-trick pony!
We don't need you
now that our gear's
already been enchanted.
What made you think
that you weren't getting cut?
[GUILD MEMBER 5]
You just gonna stand there?
[GUILD MEMBER 6]
Get out of here, loser.
[indistinct shouting]
Incompetent.
[breathes uneasily]
-Go die on the streets.
-[Rein whimpers]
Get out of here.
[REIN] I thought these guys
were my friends,
but none of them are going
to argue my case?
[all booing]
Yeah, well,
I was going to quit anyway,
'cause I've had
enough of this shitty guild.
[wailing]
[Rein continues wailing]
[coughs]
Wait, where am I? Uh?
[chuckles]
What am I even saying?
[sighs]
I can't just stand here
feeling sorry for myself.
If they're gonna do
whatever they want,
then so will I.
Those idiots don't even know
how my enchantments work.
Basically,
I enhance weapons and armor
by imbuing them
with bonus points,
a special type of mana.
But...
I hereby reclaim those points
as my own.
All enchantments I cast
for the 512 members
of the Beast's Fangs guild
are dispelled!
♪
[REIN] I'm taking back
every last point I gave them.
Oh, whoa!
Seriously? That's how many
bonus points I contributed
to the Beast's Fangs?
I can't carry it around
like this.
I've got to put them
into something.
That's pretty much all
I've got on me.
Okay, let's give it a go.
♪
Plus 10,000
into my copper sword,
which leaves 3,033 points.
I'm gonna be so OP.
What should I put
the remainder into?
Armor or a shield?
I don't have either.
[laughing]
There.
♪
Plain clothes plus 3,033.
I'm willing to bet
they offer more protection
than your standard armor!
Offense and defense enhanced.
Even though I lack experience,
I should be able to hold my own
in a fight with these.
[inhales deeply]
♪
I just realized
I've never taken a break
from working until this moment.
I always wanted to take it easy,
maybe try my hand
at adventuring someday.
Uh?
I could do
both those things now.
I'll join some other guild
and earn money
adventuring for them.
And best of all, I've got
the freedom to stay or go.
[REIN] Excuse me, I'm looking
for an adventurer's guild.
One besides
the Beast's Fangs, that is.
[BAKER] Sir, this is a bakery.
The least you could do
is purchase a croissant.
Know what?
I will take one of those!
Now, do you know of any guilds?
Nope. Still don't.
[CANDY MAKER]
You got a question,
buy something from me first.
[TOY MAKER] I'll tell you
if you purchase from my booth.
[MASK MAKER] Try on a mask.
No one's being very helpful.
[THUG 1] Hey.
[REIN] Huh?
Who, me?
Who else would we be talking to?
Yeah, you see
anybody else around?
[THUG 1] Your money.
[THUG 2] Give it here.
-[whimpering]
-Not like you have any gear
worth stealing.
[THUG 1] Wanna get slugged
in the stomach? Hand it over.
-[REIN] Oh.
-[BOTH] Huh?
[REIN] I just remembered
I'm wearing enhanced clothes.
A punch to the gut probably
wouldn't me hurt at all.
What a great chance
to test the defense
of my plain clothes plus 3,033.
-[GIRL] Hold it.
-Huh?
Would you care to tell me
what you two think you're doing?
[THUG 1] Huh?
[THUG 2] Who the hell are you?
I don't see how that makes
any difference
when your vile behavior's
clearly the bigger issue here.
What? We were just
having a little chat
-with our new friend.
-Huh?
Well, in any case,
I'm gonna call for some help.
Huh...
I didn't quite catch that,
you bitch.
You said you wanna
get beat up first?
[gulps]
-[REIN] Wait.
-Uh?
This is just between us, right?
Thank you for trying to help,
but I've got this covered,
so please step back.
This might shock you,
but I'm looking forward
to getting punched.
[GIRL] What kind
of weird situation
did I wander into?
Uh? What are you, a simpleton?
You do know
that's gonna hurt, right?
Who even asked you?
For your information, I want to
get punched as hard as possible.
Sorry, you what?
Are you a masochist?
[continues indistinctly]
You wanna get punched
in the stomach,
you bad boy! Here you go!
[both screaming]
It doesn't hurt.
My hand!
He's made of steel!!
-[thug cries]
-[all gasp]
Don't look so shocked,
you knew this would happen!
We're gonna make you pay
for this, brat, mark my words!
-[thug 1 cries]
-You better watch your back.
Snuck a metal plate under there,
didn't you?
Actually, I spent
3,033 bonus points
to enhance this outfit.
Right, if I had a bonus point
for every time I heard that one.
So are you an adventurer?
Yeah! You can call me Rein.
Nina. Hi!
[REIN] By the way, do you know
if there are any
adventurer's guilds around here?
Oh, you're looking
for a guild to join?
You... could join
the Blue Crystals. Well?
I've never heard of them.
Are you sure that
they're from around here?
Yes, I'm sure. I happen
to be a receptionist for them.
Thank you very much.
[REIN] Oh.
[NINA] If you'd like,
I'd be happy
to show you the way.
As a matter of fact,
I'm heading back there
at this very moment.
What luck! In that case,
lead the way.
[Nina chuckles] Try not to act
too surprised, though.
[REIN] By what?
[NINA] Oh, you'll see
once we get there.
♪
Disappointing, huh?
I guess you changed your mind
about joining us.
Mm-mm. No way.
I still want to register
as an adventurer here.
-What? Are you sure?
-Yeah.
This isn't some put on.
You seriously want to join?
I just said so. Why would I lie?
[NINA] Master!
I've got big news!
Someone actually wants
to register with our guild!
[guildmaster shouts]
What? No way!
Are you sure
it's not a walk-in
asking if this is
the Beast's Fangs,
finding out it's not,
and saying, "see you"?
That was funny
the first hundred times,
but it's starting
to get old. Hmm?
♪
[yelps]
[REIN] I want to join because
I left the Beast's Fangs.
Are you taking new adventurers?
[exclaims]
Yes. I knew you were
a natural recruiter, Nina.
Name's Elsie. Guildmaster
of the Blue Crystals,
your brand-new home.
Nice to meet you.
Put it there.
[REIN] Hmm?
[Rein exclaims]
[ELSIE] Well, I'm off to do
guildmaster stuff in the back.
If you need anything at all,
don't hesitate to ask.
You know Elsie.
Morning, noon, and night.
She's always happy
to lend an ear.
Nina, you take care of the rest.
Sure thing.
And this form just explains
the intermediary fees
and rewards.
Go ahead and sign, and you'll be
registered with us.
Sounds good.
[gasps]
So, this place is supposed to be
home of the Beast's Fangs?
Course not! Look around!
This guild's a complete dump!
Hold on!
So here's the deal, sweetheart.
Hand over your money
or we'll level this hellhole.
What? Who are you?
[THUG 1] We accepted a job here
the other day
that really sucked.
[THUG 2] We're prepared
to forgive you if you pay up.
Yeah, or you can
hand over that guy
and we'll call
the whole thing settled.
-Yeah, let's do that!
-Uh?
Good. Now step outside.
Sure!
[NINA] Where are you going?
You can't go outside!
Why not? It sounds like
they have business with me.
I don't know
what you're expecting,
but they're gonna do a lot worse
than just punch you!
Relax, Nina.
I took on two guys earlier.
I'm sure I can handle
these clowns.
[both gasp]
♪
See, brat, we told you
we'd get you back!
We heard about what you did
to our pal here!
You think you can get away
with this crap, you punk?
Step over here
and let's get this over with!
Rein, run away
or there's not gonna be
anything left of you.
[REIN] Hey, don't worry.
I actually expected
that something like this
was gonna happen,
so I prepared
the ultimate weapon.
[trembles] That?
Now I know you're insane.
Come on, just listen to reason.
You don't stand a chance
against them.
I'll have you know
this blade's been enchanted
with 10,000 bonus points.
And besides, being little
doesn't automatically
make you weak, trust me.
[THUG 1] What do you plan
on doing to us
with that toothpick?
[exclaims]
[REIN] Whoa!
Stop pulling on me, Nina!
[thugs yelling]
[thugs screaming]
[both gasp]
[rumbling]
[THUG 1] What was that?
[THUG 2] He isn't human!
[THUG 3] He's a crazed monster!
[THUG 4] Run away! Run away!
♪
[NINA] Uh, Rein...
What did you just do?
Nothing,
I just swung my sword a bit.
Understatement of the year.
[REIN] Oh...
[exclaims]
♪
Thankfully, no bystanders
got caught in the blast.
That's good. We got lucky.
Yeah, no kidding!
You're going to have
to be more careful.
Can you do that, Rein?
-[Rein yelps]
-Master!
You've got it, Elsie!
You're a member
of the Blue Crystals now,
and we always look out
for one another.
We've got veteran members
that can teach you skills
you never knew existed.
You'd be shocked
by how long some of them
have been adventuring.
Master's right.
I'm sure with some training
you'll eventually be able
to control your powers.
[exclaims] You really think so?
-[ELSIE] Rein.
-Uh?
Believe me,
someday, you're going to be
-one of the greats.
-[Rein chuckles]
Well, then,
welcome to the Blue Crystals!
I just wanted to let you know
the Blue Crystals covered
the street repairs
and the buildings.
So now you owe us 1,000 gold.
Wha-- 1,000?
How many years'
earnings is that?
Oh, man, your face.
Look, it's not a big deal.
Since you're working for me,
I'll just garnish it
from your wages.
Problem solved.
Hey! That makes
a whole lot of sense!
How about it, Nina?
You got any jobs
that pay a grand in gold?
Um, we do have quests,
but you need to have
some experience first.
Come on, Nina,
don't be like that.
What about that one job?
Master, I really don't think
Rein's ready
for that level of difficulty.
What job are you talking about?
[Nina groans]
Dragon slaying.
[dragon growls]
[Rein gasps]
[NINA] We received the request
nearly two weeks ago.
The client has reached out
to other guilds,
but everyone's busy,
so no one's accepted it yet.
[REIN] I will.
No offense,
but you're not ready.
Even the most high-ranked
adventurers out there
can't defeat a dragon.
They wouldn't dream
of taking one on.
Not without a few years
of experience
under their belt.
-And you--
-I say go for it.
Follow your dreams, kid.
Well, I've got
more guildmaster stuff to do.
But Master...
[REIN] The client's waiting
for a response, right?
So, I volunteer, send me!
[Nina stutters]
He looks like
a part - time dog walker
and is talking about
slaying a dragon?
You were there.
You saw what my equipment
is capable of.
This sword has
10,000 bonus points,
and my clothes have 3,033,
making them stronger
than steel armor.
Go ahead and try stabbing me
with a knife.
Who in their right mind
would try and do that?
[screams]
[REIN] Huh?
So it's true.
Cloth that's stronger
than steel armor.
You tried killing me
with a sword. [laughs]
Did you see that, Nina?
[NINA] I would have
reacted differently
if I were him.
So, who are you anyway?
Not like it matters.
But I'm Lily Flambert.
Really? I've heard of you.
[LILY] If you're so hung-up
about sending him off
by himself,
I'll go along.
[NINA] But Lily, don't you--
[LILY] It's all right.
I'm going to be just fine.
Come on, Nina,
have you forgotten
that I'm an S-rank adventurer?
[REIN] I'm D-rank!
[LILY] Yeah, I wouldn't
go around bragging about that.
Let's get moving. Rein, was it?
[Rein exclaims] Yeah.
Uh, before you go,
I need to confer
-with the master.
-[door closes]
Uh? Get back here!
-[footsteps]
-[indistinct chatter]
This city's changed
since I saw it last.
♪
[REIN]
Lily Flambert, a swordsman
who became the youngest
S-rank adventurer ever.
Her name is known
all across the continent.
At age seven,
she slew five low-level dragons.
-[dragon growls]
-[REIN] When she was only 12,
she tamed and rode
a mid-level one.
Eventually,
she became so powerful,
she started defeating
high-level dragons
without needing
anyone else's help.
But these past few years,
we haven't heard a peep
about her recent exploits.
There were a bunch
of rumors going around
about how you were
either crippled or dead,
but you don't look crippled
or dead to me.
I'm right here. You don't need
to tell me my life story.
[REIN] Could you tell me
how an adventurer like you
ended up with the Blue Crystals?
[Lily grunts]
Uh?
They're as good
as any other guild.
[chuckles]
True, so very true.
Thanks again, Lily.
I'm so glad you're here.
[LILY] I don't deserve
your thanks.
Imagine what it would do
to the guild
if you wound up dying.
[REIN] Uh?
[LILY] The Blue Crystals
would never hear the end of it
if they sent a total novice
to slay a dragon by himself.
That's the only reason
I'm going with you.
You know, I was so focused
on enchanting,
I've never fought before.
This will be my first time
besides those thugs
the other day.
Oh, yeah, be sure to let me know
if you need anything
of yours enchanted.
That's a magic sword.
That's right.
While it may be unsigned,
this powerful blade was forged
using magic techniques.
Shall I?
-Lily?
-I don't need
any of your enchantments,
rookie. Don't fall behind.
[LILY] Definitely looks like
a mid-level dragon.
A dragon? I don't see one.
I didn't mean that it's here.
I can tell from the damage.
Well, of course you can,
'cause you're
a legitimate adventurer.
[LILY] It comes from experience.
You'll pick things up
while adventuring,
whether you like it or not.
[REIN] Come on, let's go.
[chuckles]
Where are you going?
To the dragon. Hurry, this way.
If that's where we're headed,
it's this way.
[exclaiming]
What a professional!
Stop shouting about everything!
But I'm in the presence
of greatness!
What is your problem?
[running footsteps]
[LILY] Very soon.
[REIN] Uh?
[LILY] It could appear
at any time.
[REIN] Uh...
♪
[whimpers]
Lily, what's the matter?
Could you please do me a favor
and stop pestering me?
Go ahead and slay the dragon
or whatever it is
you're trying to do.
[REIN] But you and I are a team.
If you're feeling worn out,
we should catch a quick nap
or something.
At first...
I thought you were playing dumb.
Turns out you don't have a clue
what I was doing
these past two years.
Nope, sure don't.
[LILY] You wanna know
what I was really up to?
I was doing absolutely nothing,
okay?
Huh?
Uh, "nothing's" kinda broad.
Even if you took a break,
so what?
I mean you're still
the same Lily Flambert
that defeated low-level dragons
at seven,
tamed mid-level dragons at 12,
and became the youngest S-rank
adventurer ever, aren't you?
[screams]
You stupid, stupid, idiot!
[shouts] Don't you ever
stop talking? Shut up, shut up!
[♪ closing theme song playing]